dailywebsource.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy | Daily Web Source

DailyWebSource team respects your privacy and we understand the importance of the information you entrust to us. 

Below we describe what information we collect when you use our Services, how we protect that information, how long we retain it, with whom we share it, and what your privacy options are. By using the Services, you consent to our collection and use of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

What information do we collect about you?

We explain below the main ways that we collect and process information about you.

INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE TO US:

Your use of the Services may require registration, in which case we will ask you to provide certain personal information, including an email address, username, and password. You may also decide to provide us with some optional demographic information to enhance your profile, such as your country of residence, home address, education, interests, and communications preferences. 

You may also provide personal information to us, if you choose to:

  * sign up to ask a Question or answer it. Also, any similar service or request to receive certain other communications from us;
  * submit a help request, a customer services inquiry or other inquiry to us, or fill in any other forms for the purposes of receiving our Services;
  * participate in some of the features accessible via the Services (for example, message boards, chat groups, social networking, games, surveys, polls, promotions, contests, or sweepstakes);
  * contact us about employment opportunities posted to the Services; or
  * otherwise use the Services in a manner that you have requested.

Depending on which of these or any other Services you use, the personal information you provide may include your name, email address, user name, home address, telephone number, information posted by you on sites accessed via the Services. Also, if you choose to login to a product or feature accessed through a Search Application via a social networking site, you are granting us permission to access and use information about you provided by the social network. For example, if you use a social network feature to login to a product accessed through a Search Application, per such social network's policies, they may provide us access to your and your friends names, pictures, genders, user Ids, connections and any content shared using an "Everyone" or similar privacy setting. Please be aware, that by posting information to message boards, chat groups or social networking facilities available via the Services, you will be making this information available to other users of these Services to the public. You should be careful about revealing any sensitive details about yourself. 

INFORMATION WE COLLECT WHEN YOU USE THE SERVICES:

When you use the Services, we automatically collect and store certain information about your computer or device and your activities, including:

  * 1\. **IP Addresses.** We log Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, or the location of your computer on the Internet, for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. We use this information in an aggregate fashion to track access to our Services (websites and mobile applications)
  * 2\. **Device Information.** We may collect information about the browser, computer, mobile phone, smartphone or other device you use to access the Services to measure the effectiveness of those Services.
  * 3\. **Geolocation Data.** If you are using a mobile device, your mobile device's geographic location (specific geographic location if you've enabled collection of that information, or general geographic location automatically).
  * 4\. **Technical information.** This includes the information about your computer or mobile device such as type of device, mobile device ID number, web browser (Internet Explorer 8, Firefox, etc.), other browser information (e.g. size, connection speed and connection type), and operating system or platform (Linux, Mac, Windows 7, etc.)
  * 5\. Your preferences and settings (time zone, language, etc.)
  * 6\. Internet provider or mobile carrier name
  * 7\. The URL of the last webpage you visited before visiting the Website
  * 8\. Information about your activity on the Services (e.g., your search queries, mis-formatted DNS entries, search results selected, clicks, pages viewed, search history, comments).

We also use cookies and similar technologies (such as local stored objects) to collect and store information.

How do we use the information we collect?

We use the information we collect from and about you for a variety of purposes, including to:

  * respond to your queries with the best possible answers and search results;
  * understand our users (their demographics, what they do on our Services, what features they like, how they use them etc.) and improve our Services, such as by personalizing content to your interests and process and complete your transactions;
  * administer our Services, diagnose technical problems and otherwise manage our business;
  * send you communications that you have requested or that may be of interest to you in accordance with your preferences.
  * send you questions from other users that you may be able to answer if you have registered with our Services;
  * deliver prizes in connection with contests and sweepstakes or otherwise facilitate the use of our Services;
  * provide you with customer support;
  * enable us to show you ads that are more relevant to you;
  * perform functions as otherwise described at the time of collection.

We may also generate, use and disclose aggregated and/or anonymised information and statistics about your use of the Services to third parties for marketing, analytical and strategic purposes. However, no user of our Services will be individually identifiable from the aggregated and/or anonymised information and statistics.

How do we keep the information we collect secure?

We take the security of your personal information seriously and use appropriate technical and organisational measures to protect your personal information against unauthorised or unlawful processing and against accidental loss, destruction or damage. We also limit access to personal information about you to employees who reasonably need access to it to provide products or services to you, or in order to do their jobs. However, because no security system can be 100% effective, we cannot completely guarantee the security of any information we may have collected from or about you. You must protect against unauthorised access to your password and to your computer. Please sign off when you have finished using a shared computer. Your emails to us are not necessarily secure against interception so do not include sensitive information in them. We \ will not ask for passwords in an email and you should assume that if you get such a request, it might be fraudulent. YOU MUST DO WHAT YOU REASONABLY CAN TO ENSURE THE SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION. 

How long do we keep the information we collect?

We retain information for as long as required, allowed or we believe it useful, but do not undertake retention obligations. We may dispose of information in our discretion without notice, subject to applicable law that specifically requires the handling or retention of information. You must keep your own, separate back-up records. 

Age restriction

The Services are not intended for users under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under 13. If we become aware that a person submitting information is under 13, we will attempt to delete the information as soon as possible. You hereby represent that you are at least 13. 

How to edit, delete or access your personal information

You have the right to ask for a copy of any personal information that we hold about you in our records, to correct any inaccuracies and to update any out-of-date information. You can also ask us not to send you direct marketing communications (however please note that we may continue to send you service related (i.e. non-marketing) communications). If you wish to exercise any of these rights, or wish to object to our use of your personal information, please write to us on contact us page.
